

# Alexandr Kobrin Fullstack developer

#### EXPERIENCE

# **Software Engineer | Team/TechLead**DashBouquet

09/2018 - Present

- Created Custom Linux distribution kits with automatic installation
- Designed and implemented pipeline to collect and visualize 1M+ records per day
- Optimized and reduced device network traffic by 30-100 times through data aggregation and compression
- Trained NN to perform highly accurate realtime age and gender estimation (98.5% –gender and 61% – age)
- Implemented people-tracking algorithm for computer vision data
- Created 30+ small-to-medium applications for interactive screens, 3 complicated dashboards using React.
- Developed several applications with 3D-environment and physics using THREE.js and WebGL
- Oversaw teams from 2 to 8 engineers
- Interviewed more than 50 candidates for engineering positions in the company

#### Web developer

Paprikash Studio

07/2017 - 09/2018

- Made adjustments and feature-implementations for online-shops
- · Created 10+ landing pages
- Developed complex front-end solutions for sites of various themes and functionality

#### Storekeeper

PromAgroPack-2007

07/2015 - 07/2017

Developed internal web-based software for production processes automation

## EDUCATION

**Civil Engineering**Brest State Technical University 2009

- +375259470724
- ikebastuz@gmail.com
- ★ https://ikebastuz.github.io/
- Minsk, Belarus

#### SUMMARY

I am a highly motivated versatile person able to quickly investigate, evaluate, and adjust to new challenging contexts and lead a multicultural team towards effective and mutually beneficial solutions. I am an avid learner with a focus on details which makes absorption of advanced technical manuals and mastering of cuttingedge innovations my natural cup of tea. More than 7 years of experience in three successful companies where I engineered and curated through designing, developing, coding, deployment and software architecture stages more than 10 projects.

#### SKILLS

Javascript / Typescript

NodeJS

Python

PHP

HTML5, CSS3

ReactJS

REST, GraphQL, WS

AWS, Docker

CircleCI, GHActions

SQL, NoSQL, ElasticSearch

Data Science, NN

Expert

Intermediate

Intermediate

Intermediate

# LANGUAGES

Russian English Native

Intermediate

## CERTIFICATES

Yandex Data Science 04/2021 - Present

English EF SET C2 04/2020 - Present